So, are you ready for what's coming? You
better be because it's basically here.
Uh, we're going to talk about the
strange things going on in the world and
about the soon return of Jesus to
rapture his church and so much more. I
got comments of the day, question of the
day, clown world news, all kinds of
stuff. All right, you're watching the
Watching River channel. I'm glad you're
here. My name is Tom. I hope you're
well. Uh, it is a lovely day here by the
river in the middle of Connecticut. And
as far as a live studio audience goes
today, I only see one bird. That's all.
No squirrels, no cats, just one bird.
But that qualifies as a live studio
audience. Before we get to the
seriousness of our message today, I
always like to start off with the word
of God. I'm in God's promises for your
every need. It's a book that contains
scripture. I am on page 48. Jesus is
your fulfillment. We're going to read
some of these. Okay. Matthew 5 verse 6,
"Blessed are those who hunger and thirst
for righteousness, for they shall be
filled."
Psalm 37:4,
"Delight yourself also in the Lord, and
he shall give you the desires of your
heart."
Psalm 107:9,
"For he satisfies the longing soul and
fills the hungry soul with goodness."
Yes, Jesus is our fulfillment. Let's go
to Psalm 103:5. Who satisfies your mouth
with good things so that your youth is
renewed like the eagles.
Joel 26,
you shall eat in plenty and be satisfied
and praise the name of the Lord your
God, who has dealt wondrously with you,
and my people shall never be put to
shame.
John 6:35.
And Jesus said to them, "I am the bread
of life. He who comes to me shall never
hunger, and he who believes in me shall
never thirst." Give me an amen.
Thank you, my friends. Let's go to Psalm
22: 26. The poor shall eat and be
satisfied. Those who seek him will
praise the Lord. Let your heart live
forever.
Do a couple more. John 4 13 and 14.
Jesus answered and said to her, "Whoever
drinks of this water will thirst again,
but whoever drinks of the water that I
shall give him will never thirst, but
the water that I shall give him will
become in him a fountain of water
springing up into everlasting life."
That beautiful. One more. Joel 2 verse
19. The Lord will answer and say to his
people, "Behold, I will send you grain
and new wine and oil, and you will be
satisfied by them. I will no longer make
you a reproach among the nations."
Beautiful word of God. How are you guys
today? I hope you're doing well. Please
let me know in the comments how you are
doing. It's good to be here this morning
with you. It's morning for me. I know a
lot of you watch it all different times
because these podcasts are watched and
listened to from all over the world, but
I'm probably going to call this video,
are you ready for what's coming? I hope
so because it's basically here now. We
are looking at overpowering AI where the
creators of it are telling us,
you know, there is a chance of the
extinction of humanity. A small chance,
but there is a chance. Others who are
resigning from designing or being a part
of these AI companies are saying, "No,
no, no." They're saying behind closed
doors, yeah, we're in trouble, but got
to go for it. A lot of money to be made.
You know, we got mass surveillance that
is just increasing day by day. We got a
loss of privacy. They're talking UFO and
UAP disclosures. We're talking the
forming of a new world order, which
BRICS announced today, and I'll get to
that in a minute. We're seeing wars and
many, many rumors of wars. We're seeing
everything that Jesus told us would
happen. And he said, "When these things
begin to happen, look up for your
redemption drawth nigh, draws near." And
I think we're living in those days right
now. Cuz everything is changing fast,
isn't it? It's all changing so fast. The
world we lived in just a few years ago
is so different. And I'm talking I'm not
even talking about the huge turn we did
when COVID happened. I'm talking about
in the last two or three years. Life is
changing so fast because we are speeding
like a bullet toward the seven-year
tribulation. I hope you know Jesus. If
you don't, please keep watching this
video because you could have new life
today because what's coming at this
world is unbearable to even imagine
living through it. The worst time to be
alive since mankind was created is
coming to this world very soon. And I
believe that the antichrist beast system
is completely set up and ready to go. I
think the restrainer who restrains will
be removed and then he will be revealed
and that switch is ready. I don't think
anything has to happen before the
rapture of the church happens. I think
we're there. I say it all the time
because I want to hammer into your heads
that we are there. We're not waiting for
anything. We don't have to see the the
third temple built in Israel, you know,
we just know that at the halfway mark of
the 7-year tribulation, it is an
operating sacrificial
temple. So, it will be built. We don't
have to be here for that to be built. It
could be built a year after we're gone.
Some people say it could be built in two
months. Others say it'll take a year and
a half. All we know again is at the
halfway mark, the Antichrist will enter
in. and he'll stop the sacrificing and
he'll say, "Worship me." I don't see
what has to happen. I think we're ready
for the rapture of the church at any
time. I don't know the day or the hour,
but I'll tell you one thing. I think
it's getting very close. So, are you
ready for what's coming? Jesus is coming
to rapture his church in a
pre-tribulation rapture. So, I'm going
to let you know some things in the world
that are going on, and you let me know
what you think about this stuff. Does
this make for a sustainable world or are
we at a point where it's like a breaking
point on the verge of something huge?
That's what I think we are. But I'm
going to start off here. End Times
Headlines shared this. Apple insists the
new Apple Watch cannot be used for
secret surveillance. You're just not
going to believe this one. Apple has
moved quickly to insist that its latest
wearable device cannot be turned into a
hidden listening device after unveiling
a conversation recall tool that
immediately raised privacy alarms. You
won't believe this. According to a
report from Macworld, the Apple Watch
Series 12, revealed at the surprise and
shine event on Wednesday, this past
Wednesday, brings relatively modest
hardware updates, but a notable software
edition called Live Rewind.
Live rewind is launched with a double
press of the digital crown and shows the
previous seconds of a conversation as
text on the watch face. In other words,
if you're talking to somebody who's
wearing this device, they're recording
your conversation and you can listen
back to it.
The capability is meant to help when a
wearer misses a remark that cannot
easily ask for it to be repeated. It its
existence, however, implies the watch is
continuously capturing nearby speech,
often without others knowing. I would
say not often, I would say all the time.
people not knowing they're being
recorded. But like we've been talking
about recently, everywhere you go,
everything we're recorded all the time.
TVs are listening to us. If you have a
TV that's newer, meaning in the past
seven or eight years, your TV's
listening to you at all times. We talked
about those LG TVs that are recording
conversations when the TV's off and then
once you power it up, it uploads them to
the internet. It's just, you know,
incredible times. Now, this doesn't flip
me out because this is what the last
days look like. And I belong to the
master of the universe. I belong to the
King of Kings and the Lord of Lords.
He's not rattled by these last days. So,
I refuse to be as best I can by just
looking to him. Listen to this one. This
was on Prophecy News Watch. A digital ID
gatekeeper is coming to Windows. So, we
covered Mac. Now, we'll go to Windows.
For most of the personal computer's
history, the relationship was simple.
You owned the machine, opened a program,
and expected it to obey. But Microsoft
is preparing Windows for a very
different digital future.
One in which applications may first ask
the operating system what kind of person
is sitting behind the screen and whether
that person has been verified.
Microsoft's new Windows age APIs will
allow participating apps to request the
age range of a signedin user. Windows
can report that the user is under 10 or
10 to 12 or 13 to 15 or 16 to 17 or 18
and older. It can also tell the app
whether that age has been verified,
remains unverified, or whether the user
has opted out. Microsoft describes this
as a privacy preserving system. I love
how they always start off with this is
for our privacy and it's for the safety
of our children. They don't care about
your children. I think most of you
realize that. If you don't, uh, rewind
your brain to what happened during, uh,
COVID and what they did to children
during that time period. Microsoft
describes this as a privacy preserving
system because applications receive an
age bracket rather than a precise
birthday. But behind that reassuring
language sits a much larger change.
Windows is being equipped to serve as an
identity gatekeeper between the user and
the software.
The computer will not simply open the
door. It will be able to tell the app
whether the user carries the right
credentials to enter. Everything's
changing. You know, they're really
getting to a point where, you know, what
are you looking at on your computer?
That's what the computer's going to be
thinking. Well, what is this person
looking at? Oh, I don't agree with that.
It's control. It's control and it's
coming fast. [snorts] The immediate
justification is child safety. Apps
could use the signal to restrict mature
media, social features, user generated
content, communications, inapp
purchases, and virtual currencies.
Parents understandably want children
protected from predators and addictive
platforms and inappropriate commercial
practices. But a system cannot reliably
identify children without also
classifying adults. If an application
must know who is under 18, every adult
may eventually be expected to prove that
he or she is over 18. That's what's
exactly what's happening in Europe with
these digital IDs. They're saying,
"Well, in order to protect children
under the age of 16, all you adults have
to get digital IDs, you know, facial
recognition. We got to know who you are.
It's Orwellian. You know, we're living
in in that time period right now,
waiting for Jesus that we're watching
everything just set up for what's
coming." You know that seven-year
tribulation and the beast system.
I don't know if you heard about this,
but listen to this one.
Green Beret, who organized secret
pastors UFO talks, issues a chilling
warning.
Influential Christian pastors have for
months spoken in guarded terms about
closed door UFO disclosure sessions they
said were arranged by shadowy government
insiders. According to a report from
Daily Mail, private gatherings of
intelligence veterans, former service
members, and faith leaders were said to
have occurred in February, shortly
before Washington began releasing
declassified unidentified flying object
records. Remember that? I remember when
the pastors were meeting, but we didn't
know what was being said. Retired US
General Green Beret Paul Bach has now
come forward telling the Daily Mail he
helped convene those meetings to alert
church leaders to what he describes as a
dangerous new religion coalescing around
belief in extraterrestrial beings.
Box said the emerging creed teaches that
entities once worshiped as God or angels
were actually nonhuman intelligences
that people can summon. They can summon
them for healing, secret knowledge, and
spiritual advancement.
Do I think that it is leading many, many
people astray right now? Absolutely. He
said, "Do you see what's going on?
You know, this mystical religion is
developing. It's going to end up being
the one world religion, the great
delusion, the strong delusion. You know,
we're just living in incredible times.
And this stuff happens day by day by
day. It's like I never run out of
material to cover every day on the show
because there's always something
revealed that's like whoa, incredible
times we're living in.
Then this they you know we got the
bricks pow-wow happening in New Delhi,
India this weekend and uh the president
Putin is there from Russia and and Xi is
there from China and Peskian is there
from Iran and uh this morning he said
Russian President Putin says a new world
order is forming with bricks. It's like
hey you took my words because I've been
saying that for two two or three years.
Oh this is the new world order. You
know, that's why so many people say,
"What happens to the United States? How
come it's not talked about in
Revelation?" Well, I believe it is, but
not in the way people are talking about.
But, um, you know, there's a new world
order rising, and it does not include
the United States. I know that sounds
crazy right now, but you will see as
time goes on. That does not include the
United States. And BRICS is really
trying to figure out all these systems
to get around the US dollar and the
power of the dollar. and they are
calling it a new world order.
Also, President Putin from BRICS from
that BRICS summit says European leaders
are pushing toward war with Russia.
Rumors of war.
He warned Europe that sending troops to
Ukraine would trigger war with Russia
because they're talking about sending
troops to Ukraine from some of the NATO
countries.
And then he uh he met with Indian Prime
Minister Modi at the brick summit. So
they were walking together today there.
Uh also the BRICS nations jointly call
for maximum restraint in the Middle
East. You know what that means? That
means Israel stop. Stop. Leave Iran
alone. They're great.
BRICS agrees on a joint declaration
condemning unilateral war by any country
amid the Iran war.
And then right before I hit record,
Chinese President Xi says BRICS
countries must firmly stand on the right
side of history. We are living in a
world where the rising new world order
is Russia, China, Iran, North Korea. I
mean, if I had told you that 20 years
ago, you'd be like, "What?
Right.
We got this.
American University in Washington DC
yesterday hosted a militant Muslim on
9/11.
Maha Halal is an al-Qaeda sympathizer
who is also an Islamophobia expert,
whatever that means. She celebrated the
October 7th atrocities and cheered on
Palestine. She cheered them on on
Palestine and Hamas. She also whined
over Bin Laden's extrajudicial
assassination.
This is who was hosting
American University in DC was hosting
this woman for a talk on 9/11. What has
happened to the United States of
America? Then we got this. An Australian
principal of a school was effectively
pushed out of her job for refusing to
participate in an event forcing teachers
to explain transgenderism and gay
relationships to students, get ready for
this, between the ages of 4 and 12. I
don't want heterosexual relationships
explained to kids between the ages of 4
and 12. You know, but this is the world
we're living in.
All right, how's about we get to some
Middle East news.
Okay, this is from open source intel on
X. The oil pumping station on the Saudi
East West pipeline was completely
destroyed during yesterday's attack,
meaning the day before yesterday,
[snorts] according to satellite imagery
that was released yesterday. This is
incredibly important news as the East
West pipeline can transport up to
approximately 210 barrels of crude oil
per month at full capacity providing
Saudi Arabia with a major alternative to
the Strait of Horamuz. So we wondered
yesterday if that was true that the
pipeline did get blown up and at least
part of it did and they have shut it
down. They halted east west oil pipeline
operations following that major attack.
um they shut down its east west pipeline
as a precaution after reporting attacks
on the strategically important oil link.
The Saudi foreign ministry said
yesterday that the pipeline which is
capable of transporting oil from the
Gulf to the Red Sea, bypassing the
straight of Horamuz was hit by drones
coming from Iraq.
Several people were injured in the
attack in Riad and Medina regions on
Thursday and the pipeline was damaged.
The ministry said on X.
So there you go.
This is an interesting post from Amir
Sarati. He said the Saudi crown prince
chose the Mecca pact over the Abraham
Accords and he is now suffering the
consequences. Right now Saudi Arabia has
turned out to be completely alone.
America is not helping. Turkey is not
helping. Pakistan is not helping. And
now Saudi Arabia is officially no longer
sending oil through its its big
pipeline.
Uh with the straight of Horamuz blocked,
this was the main way Saudi Arabia could
still sell oil. The pipeline was their
last major route. It moves oil from the
east of the country to the Red Sea port
of Yanbu.
This means that Saudi Arabia's oil
economy lifeline is completely choked
right now.
Can you can you believe what's going on
in the Middle East with these oil, you
know, between the straight of Aramuz and
the Bab al-Mandde Strait with the Houthi
Houthies controlling that now. And then
you've had how many oil refineries
blowing up in those Gulf states in the
past few months. It's I just can't
imagine, you know, I just don't think
this is some speed bump we're going to
get through and it'll be fine. President
Trump says the US will provide
intelligence to Saudi Arabia to help
target the Yemen's Houthis, but we will
not be involved, but we will give them
intel. You know,
then this came out yesterday. Iran used
American developed artificial
intelligence models to try to target US
Navy ships in the Middle East. Great. We
we do the technology and then they use
it against us. You know, it was
according to an anthropic report warning
of emerging national security dangers.
An Iranian link group compiled
information from ship and aircraft
transponders, military photographs, and
commercial satellite photos to track
American warships and look for
vulnerabilities in their shipborne
communications. The report found
anthropics said it disrupted the plot by
the threat actor, which used the
advanced AI claude model. That was the
model they were hesitate hesitating
about releasing Claude because they they
were saying just what a few months ago
it's too powerful but it's out there now
Jack. So there you go.
Oh, Iran said it will continue. Listen
to this. Anyone who's watched this for
years and years, decades, just this will
bring a smile to your face. Iran says it
will continue cooperating with the
International Atomic Energy Agency and
they scheduled an inspection of its
Busher nuclear plant. Notice they didn't
schedule an appointment to have their
pickaxe mountain inspected, you know,
cuz that's where the real actions taking
place and everybody knows it. But yeah,
there you go. So Iran is it will
continue cooperating. Did it ever
cooperate? I mean when
then Bubba News said regarding the
Middle East yesterday because it was
supposedly they're celebrating
Rashashana yesterday but according to
you know the Bible you have to have two
witnesses spot the crescent of the moon
and that has not happened even as I
record this not yet the two witnesses
have not seen the the moon yet so really
Rashana has not begun yet but Bubba said
it's way too quiet, you know, last night
because it really there were so many
rumors of things that were going to go
on and and right now it's been quiet
there in Israel.
And then we got to mention this because
you just got to North Korea launched
ballistic missiles toward the sea
Saturday, early this morning, a day
after the US, South Korea, and Japan
completed a trilateral military drill in
response to North Korean nuclear
threats. So Kim Jong-un was like, "All
right, enough of that. launch a few of
these missiles, grab a donut, get this
done, and he got it done. So now he's
celebrating.
There you go. There you go.
The Times of Israel shared this.
Europe's climate monitor said Thursday
that August was the hottest month that's
ever been recorded around the world and
warned of worse to come as an
unprecedented super Elnino uh pattern
grows stronger.
Global temperatures over land and sea
soared to all-time highs in August and
capped an extreme summer of heat waves
and wildfires that ranked the hottest on
record for Western Europe and the
contiguous United States.
There you go. It's hot. That's what
they're saying. It's hot. Like you know
what? You think it's hot now, Jack? Get
yourself left behind. Seven-year
tribulation. There won't be one blade of
green grass. It's all going to burn. You
do not want to be here for the
seven-year tribulation. It's going to be
hot.
6.6 magnitude earthquake hit yesterday
in Jawa, Indonesia.
Um, yeah, that happened yesterday. And
as far as earthquakes, the last 24
hours, there was 48 over 4.0, 18 over
5.0, and that one over 6.0.
So, there you go. There you go. Now we
got question of the day. Question of the
day. Do you like to memorize scripture?
Is it hard for you? It's hard for me to
memorize scripture. I feel like the only
way I can do it is just by repeating it
over and over and over and over and I
still have a hard time memorizing
scripture. But do you enjoy memorizing
scripture?
And if you do, what's the last thing you
memorized? I'd love to know. Let me know
in the comments.
All right. Are you ready to go to clown
world? I'm ready. Are you ready? I'm
ready. This is clowny. Get ready for
this. I gotta get my sound effect ready.
Genuinely human. Bionic emotion sensing
humanoid robot sheds real tears while
talking. They're cry. They're crying
now. They're crying. The the robots are
crying.
Can you shed tears for me? A visitor
asked. Of course, the robot replied. and
its eyes welled up on command. What is
it? Like lemon juice or something? What
tears are coming out of a computer?
Lemon juice.
That brief exchange became one of the
standout moments at the 2026 inclusion
conference on the bund in Shanghai.
A bionic, emotions sensing robot
demonstrated its ability to physically
cry in response to a simple spoken
request,
catching visitors offguard with just how
natural the reaction looked.
Just things I never thought I'd read in
my entire life. I just could never
imagine we'd get to this point,
honestly.
The robot is built on a three-layer
technical architecture designed
specifically to generate convincing
human emotional responses rather than
simply pre-programmed animations.
Its ability to produce tears on Q points
to a deeper engineering goal, making
robotic emotional expression feel
spontaneous and responsive rather than
scripted.
Cry me a river robot. Cry me a river. I
just can't believe the things I'm
reading in Clown World in these last
days. I crying robots was not on my
dance card. I don't know about you, but
I never thought we'd be talking about
robots, you know,
crying real tears of lemon juice. Just
crazy. All right. All right. Calm down,
Tom. Let's read some comments of the
day. Okay.
This is a beautiful comment, Rita. the
Lord from creating us and carefully
knitting us in our mother's womb to
walking with us our entire lives to
giving his life for us and spilling his
blood for us to bringing us home to
spend eternity with him. This is truest
form of love and has never abandoned us.
Thank you father for your unfailing and
unending love. Amen sister. It's
beautiful. The Lord is so good. He is so
good.
Maym May.
Um, this is in response to talking about
911 yesterday and I talked about what I
was doing when I found out about the
attacks. And so I'm sharing a couple of
comments in regards to that. Maymay
said, "I was with a client in her home,
an elderly woman who was struggling with
depression and disabilities. I saw the
plane hit the tower and my first comment
was, "This is a terrorist attack. It was
a horrible sight." and just said to
myself, "Lord, help our country and
those lost, injured, and their
families." My daughter and I stood in
line for 12 hours at the Red Cross to
give blood. That day, we felt shocked
and helpless and felt we needed to do
something. And blood is always needed in
times of disaster. Yeah, that was quite
a day. That was quite a day. It was most
of us who were old enough to remember
it. I think, you know, you just never
forget feelings you had. And I still
have a hard time watching some of that
footage personally.
Raven,
25 years ago, I was at my desk at my
radio station. I was imming. That shows
your age. I aming. That means instant
messaging. Remember that? Those were the
old days on the computer. I was imming
with a colleague who had just moved to
New York. He was living within earshot
of the towers. As we were talking, he
said he saw a plane hit the tower. He
thought he was seeing things. We
immediately turned on the TV and saw
that it was true.
Sadly, he also witnessed people jumping
out of windows. Let's refle reflect and
pray for the families whose lives have
never been the same. Aba Father, may
your love touch each heart as we reflect
back 25 years. Amen, sister. Thank you.
Amen. Wow. Yeah.
Yeah. I knew people. I knew one guy who
had a meeting to go to and uh he was
running late and his wife was saying,
"You got to get there. You're running
late." and he actually, you know, wasn't
quite in the area as they as the attacks
happened. But yeah, and then I knew
another guy who was actually my cousin's
husband who who um worked in that
building and he ran out quickly and he
was one of those guys you saw running
away covered in dust and you know, just
amazing. Uh sad, you know, that was a
sad event.
What else? Here we go, Pat.
You are so right, Tom. Everything
definitely changed from that day in
2001. Life has not been the same since.
We appear to be right on the edge of the
Lord calling us home. I can't wait. This
ugly world no longer holds any appeal,
and I long to be with Jesus. Amen, Pat.
Amen.
Lucas, I hope we get raptured today or
tomorrow, but if not, this is a
beautiful dress rehearsal for that one
glorious day when Jesus comes to take us
home and we finally get to be with him
forever. Marinatha. Amen, brother. I
like that dress rehearsal. Yeah. Because
one day soon we will hear that trumpet
sound, the voice of God, and we will be
home with Jesus. We will meet him in the
clouds and he will take us to where he
is, to that place that he has been
preparing a a dwelling place for us for
2,000 years. And he's going to take us
there. He's going to receive us to
himself. And that day is coming soon.
And I just want as many people aboard
the ark as possible. So if you don't
belong to Jesus or you're not quite
sure, hear me out. We'll talk about the
good news, the gospel, and and maybe
today will be a day that your entire
life changes. I don't know. Could be.
But we all need a rescue because we're
all sinners. We all fall short of the
glory of God. We're not perfect. We
think things that are a little weird
sometimes. We've done things we're
ashamed of in our lives. And we need a
rescue. And you know what? God didn't
say when we fell and sinned, like,
forget about them. No. God sent his only
begotten son, Jesus, that whoever
believes in him will not perish but will
have everlasting life. You see, the most
high God doesn't want anyone to perish,
but that all would come to repentance.
He wants everyone to believe in his only
begotten son. He sent Jesus here, and
Jesus came here will willingly 2,000
years ago, born of a virgin, conceived
by the Holy Spirit. And why did Jesus
come here? You know, we know about all
the beautiful things he did, the healing
and the love and the miracles and the
teaching. But you know what? He came
here, the lamb of God slain from the
foundation of the world. He came here to
die on that cross to shed blood because
without the shedding of blood there is
no forgiveness of sin. Blood has to be
shed. It's been that way since before
the foundation of the world because sin
is so offensive to the most high God
that in order for him to remove,
forgive, erase sin, blood has to be
shed. And in the Old Testament, they
would slaughter the animals and sprinkle
the blood in the Holy of Holies and
their sins would be covered for a year.
But that's not the way it is now because
Jesus came here and made the
once-for-all payment for sin. His blood,
the blood he shed, has the power to
forgive and erase and remove every sin
that has ever been committed by
everyone. But the thing is, you have to
with your free will believe that. You
have to understand that a a serious
price was paid to make your sin go away.
But once you say to Jesus, "Jesus, I I
know I'm a sinner. I admit I'm a sinner,
and I know I need payment for these
sins, and I can't provide the payment.
My best behavior doesn't pay for my sin
or erase it. Only you have that power,
Jesus. And I now have faith in your
blood that you shed that it'll wash me
white as snow and completely remove my
sin problem from me." And Jesus, I
believe in your finished work on the
cross. I know you were nailed to the
cross and you shed that blood and you
died and you were buried and you rose
again the third day. I need a savior and
you are the perfect only savior in the
world. So I am turning from my self
where I'm always living for myself to
all of a sudden I'm turning to believing
in the gospel, believing in the atoning
blood you shed. And at that moment of
belief when you finally are like Jesus
I'm done. I'm a sinner. I need you. I
believe in your powerful blood. I
believe in your finished work. At that
moment, you are born again because God
will place the Holy Spirit in you and
you will be sealed until the day of
redemption. He won't let you out of the
palm of his hand because he wants to
spend forever and ever and ever with
you. And you know what? At the moment of
conception, you became an eternal being.
I don't care if you believe or you don't
believe. You are going to be somewhere
for eternity. And the two choices are
with God forever in paradise or
separated from God forever in a place
that wasn't created for mankind. You
know what was created for mankind?
Jesus and that rescue plan. You know
that's what was created for mankind,
that rescue. But if you say, "I don't
want that rescue," you're going to end
up in a place described of as weeping
and wailing and nashing of teeth and
hot. I wouldn't want my worst enemy to
go there. And you won't say you're
unfair. You'll say, "I heard the gospel.
I heard that my sins were paid for by
the blood of the lamb. That offer was
right in front of my face." And I kept
saying, "I don't want that. I don't have
to believe that. That's ridiculous. Oh,
man. I don't want to have to be a Bible
banger." You don't have to be a Bible
banger. You have to understand that
you're a sinner who needs a rescue. And
God provided the rescue. And you put
your faith in that atoning blood and in
his finished work on the cross, and
you're saved. And if you don't do that,
you're going to face Jesus on judgment
day, and you're not going to be saved.
You're going to be led off to eternal
separation, and you are going to say,
"Tom, I wish I could come back and
listen to your gospel one more time, but
it will be too late." My goodness.
Please take it serious. It's the most
important decision of your entire life.
It really is. There's nothing that
compares. This has eternal
ramifications. You will be somewhere
forever and ever. Okay? Choose Jesus
today. Choose to believe in him. Believe
in that gospel, the good news. It's very
simple. Jesus did all the hard parts.
But I know that wide is a path to
destruction. I know that many more will
say no to this than will say yes. But my
goodness, I hope you heard me and I hope
you make the right decision today. Okay?
I prayed for you because before I
recorded this video in my prayer time
this morning, I said a prayer for every
single person that would watch this
video. And that includes you. So like it
or not, you have been prayed for today.
And if we're not raptured today, and you
know me, I say it every day. Today is a
perfectly good day for the rapture. But
it's not up to me. It's up to God. And
I'm glad it's up to him. But if not
today, God willing, I will see you guys
tomorrow. I love you guys.
>> Oh Jesus, [music]
master, [music]
creator.
We are the alpha. [music]
Omega,
you're the king of kings.